Guide to the Brian McGinn Papers AIA.015
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XI: Korean War Veterans, 1951-2004; 1.95 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 18 folders in a second record carton, and 6 folders in a third record carton.
  - Quinn, Thomas S. (includes photograph), 2000-2003 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Republic of Korea: Korean War Service Medal, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - "The Royal Ulster in Korea" Hamill, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Royal Ulster Rifles, 2000-2003 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Scully, William (includes photograph), 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Sheahan, Patrick (includes photograph), 1951-1952, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Stories: St. Petersburg Times, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Taejon Massacre: Columban Missionaries, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Treaty of Friendship 1950: Military Service, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Ward, Thomas John (includes photograph), circa 1950, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Western People, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - White, John Patrick (U.S. Marine Corps), 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - White, Patrick A. (includes photograph), 1951-1952, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Woods, Father Frank (Co. Louth), 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - World War II Casualties Repatriation: U.S. Army - Europe, 1948-1949, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Series XII: Vietnam War Veterans, 1966-2003; 1.35 Linear Feet in 28 folders in a record carton and 1 legal sized manuscript box.
  This series contains materials related to veterans of the Vietnam War including documentation on granting of posthumous citizenship to several soldiers. This series also contains photographs of individuals soldiers.
  - Anti-War: Singers, 1966-2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Articles: Vietnam, 1995-2002 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Australians in Vietnam, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - B, 1999-2005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Bacroft, Philip Sean, 1999-2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Canadians in Vietnam, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Casualties: McGinn's List, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Clippings: Central and South America, 1982-1989 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Clippings: Draft Dodging and the Dan Quayle Controversy, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Clippings: Korea, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Clippings: MIA/POW, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Clippings: Vietnam, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Collopy, John Patrick (4th Infantry Division): Posthumous Citizenship, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Coyle, John, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Coyne, Michael: "Green Fields of Vietnam" Documentary, 1997-2002 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - D, 1999-2005 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Donovan, Pamela Dorothy (Nurse), 1986-2000 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Donovan, Pamela Dorothy: FOIA II, 1967-2002 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Driver, Jim, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Essays: Vietnam, 1968-1986 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Fitzgerald, Terence Patrick, 1967-2003 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Freyne, Bernard ("Brian") Anthony, 1967-2001 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Gallagher, Patrick, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Howell, Edward, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Irish in Vietnam: Missing Information, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Irish Veterans I (mostly articles), 1968-2001 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Irish Veterans II (mostly articles), 1968-2007 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Irish Veterans Memorial Project, 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Landers, Edmond John, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - M, 1996-2003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - N, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Notes, 1986-1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - O, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Rescorla, Richard (Articles), 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Reynolds, Richard Peter, Jr., 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - S, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - San Francisco Vietnam Memorial, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Porter, Tom, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Vietnam Memorial (Washington, DC), 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)